Guide to the Alice Louise Clark student letters and photographs
Stanford University Libraries.
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives.
Alice Louise Clark student letters and photographs
1918-2014, bulk 1932-1937
1932-1937
SC1202
Clark, Alice Louise
0.75 Linear feet (2 boxes)
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives. Stanford University Libraries. 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: speccollref@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
This collection was given by Jeanne Harris Armstrong to Stanford University, Special Collections in 2014.
Information about Access
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
ALice Louise Clark earned her AB in Political Science from Stanford University in 1937.
Scope and Contents
Materials include letters and photographs from Clark's time at Stanford, as photographs of Clark's family. Also included is a biographical document written by Jeanne H. Armstrong.
Access Terms
Armstrong, Jeanne Harris; Student life.; Women college students--California--Stanford.
Collection Contents
- Letters
  - Introduction by Jeanne H. Armstrong, Her Daughter, 2014 Apr 16 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journal + Graduation Exercises, 1932-1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Pre-Req Dinner (Stanford Chaparral), Circa 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing Letter (Alice Clark), 1935 Sep-Nov (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Incoming and Outgoing Letters (Alice Clark), 1936 Jan-Jun (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Incoming and Outgoing Letters (Alice Clark), 1936 Jul-Dec (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing Letters, 1937 Jan-Aug (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Letter from David (From Mexico), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing Letters (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Photographs
  - Sarah Gossion Portrait (to Duncan Pre-Marriage) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Group Photo Including Alice as a Girl (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Idaho Springs, Colorado, 1918 Dec 12 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Portrait of Alice Louis Clark (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - D. E. Clark Family Photo (Ventura), 1933 (Box 2, Folder 5)